https://amma.org/privacy-policy

Amma means Mother
in many languages.
Her real name is
Mata Amritanandamayi.
How She Began
Born in a remote coastal village in southern India, Amma first began to embrace the people in her village as a way to ease their suffering.
What People Say
Here's how a few world leaders and journalists have described their experiences with Amma.
Awards & Honors
Best known for her embrace, Amma also oversees an award-winning network of international charities.
North America Tour
Amma's 2020 North American Tours were canceled due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
Retreats with Amma
We were forced to retreat from the 2020 Retreats with Amma due to the COVID-19 pandemic.
What to Expect at a Program
Read our Guides for Newcomers.
Charitable Organizations
Active in 40+ Countries,
Amma Disciples' Tour Schedules
Details of satsang programs conducted by Amma's monastic disciples in various cities in the Americas.
IAM Meditation Technique
A short and simple approach that anyone can learn, always taught free of charge.
International Headquarters
Amritapuri is located in the picturesque village of Vallikavu, in the southern Indian State of Kerala.
Amma has never asked anyone
to change their religion.
Only to go deeper
into their values or faith,
and live by those
essential principles.
Love
"Be like the honeybee who gathers only nectar wherever it goes. Seek the goodness that is found in everyone."
Serve
"Don't be discouraged by your incapacity to dispel darkness from the world. Light your candle and step forward."
Conserve
"Where did we go wrong? The real mistake we commit lies in our inability to differentiate between requirements and luxuries."
Effective January 1, 2010
M.A.Center is committed to safeguarding the privacy of its on-line users' Personal information. Please read the following policy to understand the rules and procedures followed by M.A.Center in handling Personal information provided to us over the Internet. If you have further questions regarding our privacy policy please contact us via email at privacy@amma.org.
What information does M.A.Center collect?
M.A.Center collects the Personal information only from persons who contact us and voluntarily provide the information to us or that is given to us by various affiliated Amma organizations (satsangs and centers) that have your permission to share your Personal information. “Personal information” means your name, shipping/mailing address, telephone number, fax number, email address, credit or debit card account number and may include your retreat registration and donation preferences.
How M.A. Center uses the Personal Information
We use your Personal information to respond to and fulfill requests for products and services including:
1. sending information about the activities of Amma, M.A.Center and our affiliates
2. sending you our e-newsletters
3. contacting you about the status of your orders, donations and retreat registrations
4. completing your purchases and retreat registrations
5. completing your donations
When we disclose personal information to others
1. M.A.Center does exchange Personal information with various affiliated Amma organizations (satsangs and centers) in the U.S. and abroad so that they can contact people on the mailing list about Amma programs and events.
2. M.A.Center's mailing list, including the Personal information we receive through the Internet, is never shared with any commercial organizations and is never sold, rented or given to unrelated third parties.
3. M.A.Center will disclose Personal information to third parties if we believe in good faith that the law requires us to do so.
Right to control and correct Personal information
1. Individuals who wish to register online for Amma retreats are asked to open an “account” in which they provide a user name and password. Individuals can access their account to change that information during open registration time simply by clicking on “Register online” link. Please contact us at privacy@amma.org at any other time to change that information.
2. Individuals who wish to receive information about MA Center activities via the E-newsletter provide name and email address. Individuals can change the information at any time by accessing their account themselves. For this, log into lists.ammagroups.org, then enter the email address. Choose 'Forgot Password' if password is not available, and a new password will be emailed to the given email address.  Follow the instructions in the email to access the account and update it.
Or email us at admin@ammagroups.org, to update your preferences
3. Individuals who purchase goods or services from the bookstore or who give donations are asked to supply their Personal information at each transaction. Individuals can change the information at any time by emailing us at privacy@amma.org
How we protect your Personal information
1. M.A.Center uses a secure server with 128 bit encryption to assure the security of the data being transmitted to M.A.Center. M.A.Center's database is protected from unauthorized access by a series of highly sophisticated software protection programs.
2. M.A.Center secures the Personal information, including credit card numbers, received from individuals who make online purchases from M.A. Center. Our secure server software provides protection for your Personal information. We encrypt all of your Personal information, including credit card number, name, and address, so that it cannot be read as the information travels over the Internet. This data is used only to confirm our existing records. Sensitive data is also encrypted while being stored on our server.
3. M.A. Center limits access to your Personal information to those persons that are required to fulfill the requests for information, services or products. Your Personal information is password protected with access only to those selected and authorized persons.
4. M.A. Center provides links to affiliated entities. These sites operate independently of M.A. Center. M.A. Center is not responsible for the privacy, terms of use or other policies of any other web site.
How we use Cookies
1. M.A.Center does use cookies to store information. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored in your computer's hard drive.
2. M.A.Center gives the option to the user to store their personal preferences as cookies. These cookies are for your convenience only, and are not used for any other purpose.
3. However, M.A.Center uses cookies to track the items you place in your shopping cart during a single shopping session. Therefore your browser must accept cookies if you wish to shop at our online bookstore www.amma.org/bookstore. These cookies identify your computer and contain no Personal Information.
Travel exchange bulletin board
1. M.A. Center provides a travel exchange bulletin board. M.A. Center does not and has no obligation to monitor this bulletin board.
2. If you use the Travel exchange on this site, please be aware that any Personal information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of this board, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the Personal information you choose to submit to this bulletin board.
Amendment of Policy
M.A. Center reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy any time. No individual notice of such changes will be provided but they will appear on the website in the form of a revised and newly dated Privacy Policy. Our current policy was amended January 1, 2010.
Contact Us
legal@amma.orgwebsupport@amma.orgwebeditor@amma.org
North American Tour
Retreat Registration
Travel Exchange
Websites to Explore
Embracing the World
Amrita University
Login  |  Terms of Use  |  Privacy Policy  |  Copyright © M.A. Center 2019 |   Mata Amritanandamayi (Amma)
Share
